Yeah, it's not.
So in the parameter file under global
section,
we would have ABC Aurora connection.
And this snowflake connection is I told
you right whenever in our ABC components
if you observe we have few snowflake
connections currently all those are named
as connection con ABC snowflake like that
I have given under common folder once if
we are using it for any domain specific,
we would be taking all the components
from common ABC to the domain specific
ABC folder, right?
Once we are bringing here, we're updating.
We have to update the snowflake
connection name wherever we are using in
the ABC components to the corresponding
connection name.
So here this is the naming standard that
we that we have to follow for a
connection cont EJT and then domain name.
So for broker,
it should be broker for claims it should
be cont EJT claims like that.
OK, all the components,
all the ABC components and the mainstage
load mappings or target load mappings all
have to use a single snowflake connection.
OK,
Connect the name also getting sent Yeah,
name has to be changed.
This is the requirement.
Like this is the requirement we got asked
me to do so name should also be changed.
OK And like how do you do it?
Like do you do it in a bulk or how do you
do it?
I'm doing it manually.
Like there are I think around six to
seven components which are holding these
snowflake.
You can also jot them,
jot them down you as you're already going
through end to end flow today, right?
Jordan,
like jot down all the components where we
are using snowflake connection so that it
would be easy for you to like change it.
Otherwise you can give the list to the
developer,
corresponding developers who are doing
that whenever an issue comes.
OK and after that this is the ABC
connection name,
ABC database name are related and this is
ABC schema name.
These two are related to Snowflake ABC OK
and then these are related to stage table
are a table main array table.
These three are related to main array
table.
These three are related to temp array
table and then source name, domain name,
target zone all these are related to get
the metadata entries like all the all of
them.
And the last one is the parameter which
is used for read and purposes the
execution run ID.
OK and here why I have given multiple
because earlier I what is this one second
source zone What is that parameter?
Which one source zone No no 78 this is
source zone zone 1 stage 2 what is the
space?
We are not choosing it anywhere but I
think we are using it in the batch
prerequisite task flow or ETL data
indication where we are checking OK so we
are in case if any of my job load fails,
we would be sending out a notification
right there.
I think I I'm using this source zone to
provide the source zone.
So now I have zone 1 as my source
tomorrow for zone 3,
maybe zone 2 can be the source so but
what is stage 2, stage one?
This OK, this is their,
this is their zone 1 Stage 2 is there is
where we have the iceberg table,
snowflake iceberg they're calling that
layer at like this zone 1 stage 2.
So every time this value will be same,
it will change.
It depends, it depends on the table.
For now,
we are proceeding like we are developing
fuel wave 1 assets, right.
I think all these assets are having
similar kind of thing.
All these assets are pointing to zone 1
tables which are in zone 1 stage 2.
Maybe if for wave 2 or wave three,
if the tables layer, target layer changes,
maybe source change towards zone,
source zone would also be changes.
It depends.
I don't know all the values like it's
like it's it, it's, it's normal, right.
We would be getting the things when we
are progressing in the designs or in the
build or in the work.
OK, as of now we are using this,
but it can be changed depending upon the
tables just a moment.
So it's a point of this so soon,
it's the name now pattern so soon pattern
too soon.
Currently for wave 1 tables,
I don't know for all the wave 1 tables
right broker and account as you are
documenting I'm telling,
but I'm thinking for all wave 1 assets
John 1 is the source.
But if I if you want the confirmation,
you have to check with Spym or Gayathri.
Yeah,
but for producer and this CCO John 1 is
the source.
OK, source system code.
OK, source source name, domain name,
target drone, application layer name.
These four are user for fetching the
batch metadata.
And this is source system code which
would be used to populate source system
code in the target table.
OK, and this is user for rerun scenario.
I'm going to the top.
This is these are the local sections
first for job preload.
For job preload we have to provide the DQ
check indicator and job name and target
object stage table object stage table
object name.
All these are I'm I'll be using them for
clean up or doing the calculations.
OK, the job name,
job name I will be using for to fetch the
job ID from the job metric data table.
First is to like if we can skip in case
if, if this value is N right?
So we,
this is used like in in the task I showed
you right in the decision task,
we'll be checking if there is any DQ
cheques are assigned to this table.
If there are not,
then we will we can skip this right?
So based upon the design,
I will be passing it from here.
OK.
And this is user for job for fetching the
job ID.
Target object, stage table object,
stage table name.
All these I'm using for you know for what
is this stage table object and stage
table name are same right?
Yeah,
it is same but I think I'm using some
different names.
This is in the query but this is at the
object level data object level.
It's OK if we if we don't pass these two.
Also it is OK we can give any common one
table because the in target cleanup on
stage count target tables are dummy right.
We don't need them,
but I've just added them in case, OK,
and error types error, of course,
all these things, right?
All these things we would be needing as
part like in in case of any failure,
we have to make an entry into job error
stats, right?
For that we would be using.
So this error type is related to network
error.
So if I'm doing a restart and while while
I more in most of the cases,
we'll do a restart in case of a network
failure in the previous run.
So in the previous run because of network
failure,
we won't be able to update the what?
We won't be able to update the job run
status right.
So here it will update the job status to
fail and then it will make an entry into
No,
no no it don't update the status as fail.
It will use the same entry.
In case of a restart,
it will use the same entry in the job run
stats to do the restart run also.
But it will make an entry into job run
stats.
For that we would be using error type,
error code from here OK and this error
code,
error code and error message and error
type is used whenever any source table
load gap got failed OK and after that in
the job post load failure we are just so
one one thing.
So if there is no redone or any restart
right then in that case if you put this
as null that is also fine right?
This is parameter I didn't get too real.
So this error related parameters like is
it for every time to?
Yeah,
every for each and every table we have to
pass them because we cannot assign
directly at the task flow level.
We have to provide them via no.
But if it is not a restart or rerun then
do we still need it?
Oh whatever normal run also.
So this only this is used for restart
scenario Yeah.
Otherwise rest of all we don't know.
Even in like all these errors occurs in a
normal run only correct?
Except this Except this all will occur in
a normal run.
Any of the error scenario can be raised
during a normal run only.
OK,
OK yeah can we proceed Restart is fine
but this this particular 1213 and 14 like
how do you know like which type of error
will be there?
Like how can we can we put the value that
source dependency error or something?
Yeah,
all these parameters are being used in
the respective components in the IDMC
already.
So all these parameters are part of job
preload.
So these will be applied wherever they
are.
They are present whenever the scenario
comes,
whenever the particular transformation
getting executed or component getting
executed.
OK.
And here for job post load success like
we have error type job error code and
error message like this OK and then any
failure,
any execution failure we would be
triggering this right?
OK.
And after that we have job post loss
access.
So here first one is the target
expression which is used as part of
balance reconciliation.
And this is the ball reckon Philtre this
would be used.
I told you all this already the scenario
when we when we have to use and then
coming to source record balancing error
type.
So source record sorry record balancing
error flag.
This is related to the record count
balancing flag.
If it is otherwise why we have we have to
use this.
So similarly all the error types that we
would be passing in job run strats post
load success,
we are making entry into job run Strat in
case of a failure right?
All the combinations of failures are
jotted down and all these are users
separately based upon the scenario these
are handling No.
Which of these needs to be like value
needs to be always same and which of
these are like we need to change depend
upon scenario.
All these things needs to be populated
respective like if let's OK, OK, you're,
you're saying if there is no balance
reconciliation,
then in that case we might not need this.
That's what you're saying, right?
Then in that case,
if you don't use any balance
reconciliation stuff also no, no,
not like that.
That is one question.
But also I'm saying like the previous one
or this one, right?
Every time like will this error types and
this sentencing the error type,
every time these values will be same or
this might change like in the parameters.
No these won't change.
These won't change.
Every time this would be same.
OK and these are just sentences Sriya.
We would be passing job ID, job run ID,
whatever the dynamic things right inside
the error message,
we have them in the logic already as
dynamic only.
OK,
And the all these are related to job post
load.
And this is for job post load success.
So here they like job post load failure.
This is one of the component for that
also we have to provide all these things,
OK.
And then this is for the job preload
failure.
And this is at the mapping task level.
These are related to the source query.
OK, that's it.
Yeah, I'll share it with you.
Yeah.
OK after that mail OK so here I have
given few component names OK we are like
first one is just I made some updates
here and I have given the details there.
You can ignore this here I our first top
like I told you right,
First we have to copy all the basic
component to the domain specific.
So after that we have to change update
the connection name from this to this
connection TGT domain name.
So these are the mappings that I jotted
down for update.
But I can see few other mappings are also
there.
So as you are already going through the
this,
just have all the mapping names ready so
that you can share it with the team.
OK after that.
So for every development first thing is
ABC we have any common frameworks or
present in DIAA common folder.
So under ABC we have ABC components.
We have to copy all of them to the domain
specific ABC folder.
After that we have to change the
snowflake related connection names.
After that we have to create batch pre
request.
We have already this batch pre requested
task flow present in the ABC folder.
We have to move that for move that task
flow to actual main task flow and
otherwise we can use.
We can change its name and parameter file
whatever.
We have to provide the appropriate
parameter file name or directory name and
whatever required in that input field we
have to provide them and we can use it
directly.
And for batch level task flow,
job level task flow,
we have these already created for some
other some other domains right?
We can take a copy of them to our
specific folder and we have to make sure
each and every ABC component should be
pointing to the whatever the domain ABC
folder component which we have should has
to pop component its own ABC component
not to common ABC or not to any other
domain.
OK here I'll tell you an example.
If I am I'm working on claims broker is
already done.
I copied job level task flow and batch
task flow from broker and when I like
when I copied all the task flows,
sub task flows all the components within
that folder are pointing to broker ABC
components.
We have to manually update it to our ABC
components and we have to apply all the
input fins all these things.
This has to be done for one table and for
the next time onwards we can use this
component to copy within our domain.
OK,
rather than every time getting from
broker and updating basics to reduce the
effort,
we can do this and it same goes the batch.
So this batch prerequisite will not be
there in ABC rather it will be there in
main.
Because the components we don't need to
change every time we are only one
component would be there and some
notification related stuff would be there
with some decision and all.
So as the structure is same always,
we just need to change the name and
description and the input field values
which are just parameter file directory
and parameter file name.
I kept it under common folder only so
that every every time they can directly
get it from there right?
So even the component also after copying
that the component automatically points
to this domain specific ABC component
only.
That is the reason why I have added it in
the common.
OK.
And then can you provide like 1 sample
like you you had shared couple of the I
have the click recording already.
I'll give you that.
I want to do as part of this ABC three
steps.
I,
I'll give you and any standard task flow
which I can copy which is final,
right That yeah,
I can come past task flow every multiple
teams are working.
Yeah,
we're not sure who is changing when there
is no checkout check in process also not
in actually we are doing currently.
So people are changing things.
But if you know the gist of the framework,
you can get it.
But for now,
I can give you 1 task flow which is
account which I can see it is valid and
no one is touching it.
OK, I'll give you that.
OK.
And the OK, and one more thing,
there's all these task store names, right?
So that usable component name,
the list of the ABC components,
where is it next door?
Is it, I think it's not there in LLD,
right?
The component's name and component called
yeah, it's, it's technical, right?
It it won't be part of LLD now.
So where is it like that?
It's not there.
It's not document for it RIA like I'm
giving you the folder name already, right?
Folder name and folder name and all the
components in that are final.
Yeah,
but that needs to be documented somewhere
right in Lily's find.
Otherwise I cannot be there in it will be
that some to some file.
It needs to be there, right?
OK, let me add it here.
Only IDMC folder name you need right?
Let me add it here.
Not only I didn't see folder name,
actually the component name basically I
can also feel it.
That is not a problem,
but that needs to be there somewhere.
I'm not saying it's to be yeah, yeah,
that needs to be added here.
You, you can add it here.
That is needed because each time like we
were like tries to understand if it's
right, they need the component details,
OK, This is Dai common ABC OK,
you can add it and after that, OK,
So these are the things that needs to be
casted.
So what I have written the two mappings
of change, OK.
So while we are,
I told you already while we are fetching
any run details from June 1 tables for
June 1 tables we have we are using view
some views, right?
Yeah.
I I'm just letting you know we are using
some views, OK.
And then value of application source
batch it in the metadata should be
updated.
OK we have application source batch ID if
this should be updated as with the
actually.
So while I was doing the POC I have
created some dummy metadata entries even
for source batch ID and I asked the team
to update it with the appropriate batch
ID.
Even teams now are creating dummy
metadata entries but this has to be
updated with the actual John 1 batch ID.
This is for the whole team.
But like if any issue comes with this
like if you face it in future like ask
the team like this is kind of a trade
equal.
I check that needs to be done before
moving any component to other SIT OK and
the value of schema name and job metadata.
So all these also they have created
source tables,
target tables and testing schema.
But once after after having all the
tables in place in the actual schema,
now the data model and databases and
schemas are created in Snowflake.
Now people are using the exact tables
only.
But earlier then they were not using the
correct schemas and databases.
They they may be loaded,
they they may be loading it right.
But if they don't change the schema name
and database name, what we'll do?
ABC component will fail automatically
because as the database name and schema
name is already given in the geometry
data table,
we would be using the same values to
calculate the target count.
Source record count is 1 and target
record count will be always 0 otherwise a
different number as the values are not
appropriate.
So these issues might come.
That is the reason why I I've just
highlighted whatever the issues or
mockups that are that team are performing
to do the work build now,
but which needs to be revised later.
OK.
And the values of count,
threshold indicator,
amount threshold indicator,
they are keeping them directly and
because I have kept it and they are also
keeping it and or if I have kept Y,
they're also keeping it Y,
It should be based upon the functionality,
right?
If they are,
if there are any balance metrics related
to amount or count based upon that they
have to update, right?
So this this also one of the check that
they have to construct and the entries in
the ATL data injection,
all these things should be maintained ATL
data injection metadata.
So they're giving like while I was doing
the beauty, I have given only one table.
So they're also giving only one table.
I should know it should not be like that.
If they have multiple source tables then
multiple entry should be made into the
CTL 8 and this in my data table right?
So that's how it has to do.
And also for role master I have given
only one entry for identifier only one
column.
But in sorry in Rule master I have given
only one entry for null.
So if in case of any new rule has come
fast,
it has to be made made into it has to be
entered into the rule master then only we
have to use that.
So that functionality they are missing
it's what I'm feeling.
And then job relation also we have to I
assigned the rules as per the
functionality and also balance
reconciliation metadata OK after that OK
After that third party entries for
testing OK.
So here as the currently as there is no
first time incremental logic in place for
ABC,
we have we are making some dummy entries
into these your batch runsters,
job runsters and each in the transition
source window.
For these things we are making some dummy
entries.
And also in while I was doing UT for CC
why I found that even for source job run
or batch run, the entries are not proper.
So I asked the team to mock up even the
source related entries to handed first
time incremental and the current run
which which they were doing currently for
testing or build.
OK further to also have a recording.
I'll I'll give you how to do how we are
doing those entries.
But suppose we are testing something,
then application source batch ID to get
it like whom do I like have to reach out
like, yeah.
So yeah, how I figured out for CCO,
I'll tell you.
So when I come to CCO, I asked guy,
guy three,
what is the source table that I'm using
or the source batch that I'm considering?
What is the source domain name,
source source name,
domain name and play application layer
name for that particular source batch.
Based upon that I got the batch ID.
After getting the batch ID I queried
using my target table sorry source table.
So I found one thing and what is the
table name that I have in one is some CCO
DB scoop 1,
some table name OK CCO DB scoop one or
the database and schema names of the
Teradata table or some CCO actual CCO
source table?
Those are just prefix which are added to
each and every iceberg table.
But those are not part of the entries.
So then I go to know, OK,
this prefix is not this who we have to
use their table.
And directly I checked with the developer
who made that entry,
we have that ID in place for batch ID or
job ID, right?
Their entries, I e-mail ladies,
we find it, right.
So using that,
I reached out to the developer and I
asked whether this is the table that is
loaded as part of this and this is the
entry that you're using.
They said yes.
So based upon that,
I created entries into my ETL ETA
injection metadata because there I need
source table name, right?
So I should have the same table name
which they are using in their job
metadata entries.
Then only my match would be successful.
So this here we have to pay much
concentration OK pay some attention OK
And after that DQ check indicator.
So this has to be kept Why?
If only if DQ cheques are applied as per
the discussion.
OK,
So these John man and John are having
same ABC tables only but don't do is
using few more extra.
So ABC tables than John compared to John
they're not doing some decreasing,
they are not performing but we are
performing all of them, right.
So we have some extra tables all of them.
What I got to know from John when ABC
lead or John when ABC team is they are
they have created as new database in
Aurora using some liquid base,
liquid basis.
I don't know Liquid base is some kind of
technology or a tool which they are using.
OK they're they're creating some database
where the database name,
schema name might change.
As per the this standard.
It is not done and we didn't get any
information about it till now.
OK they told they will inform but they
didn't inform me.
This is the one important thing which
needs to be like take which needs to be
you know handled.
Whenever we get any such communication
from zone one we have to update the
database name and schema name in all the
static parameters because all in
everywhere.
Currently we are using default DB and ABC
metadata only.
If the database name gets changed we have
to update all the parameters because
these parameters are being deployed to
the other environments right?
They are planning to use have the new
database set up in the other environments.
OK as of so Ardora DB will not be used,
might not be used.
Yeah,
Ardora only in Ardora only they're
they're creating some different database
using some liquid base like which is to
some liquid base.
I don't know exactly the details about it,
but this is there.
And in during the poll occasion also,
I asked him if there is any kind of
information related to that and if the
team needs to use the new database setup.
I asked him to let us know,
but I didn't see any mail regarding that
information.
OK,
That's the reason why we have this as a
risk.
OK, So then in if that change comes,
then all the edition related like
parameter entries needs to be changed.
Yeah, only in the ABC database I, I,
I given I have given here the two
parameters which needs to be changed that
change after that as per and one more.
So you said that connection name will be
changed right?
According to the domain.
So the connections are already created or
that also needs to be created.
Only connections are handled by Guy 3.
So based upon the build progress we are
doing the work on on this connection.
So for claims if we need she's working on
that claims connection.
I'm not sure she has created for all the
domains at least for wave 1.
Not sure on it Priya OK,
but any build activity that we are taking
up guide through would be the would be
responsible for the connection creation
is like I I know she was only doing
earlier,
but now I think I don't know whether
she's taking that accountability or
someone is taking care of it.
I'm not sure on it,
but you can reach out to guys if she will
provide you the correct POC.
OK and and next earlier snowflake data
model is not appropriate.
Now the domain level databases came into
picture and schemas came into picture.
Earlier it was not the case.
So I have given if even in the parameter
file.
If you see I have given some testing kind
of schema like that only.
So I ask a team these all these values we
are using in ABC.
So all this should be updated properly in
the parameter file.
OK, OK, this alignment is is already done.
This is what the final like whatever we
have discussed for pass request,
that is the final alignment, OK.
And after that these are just OK.
These are just OK.
It is just valuation date, OK,
This one I told you right already
valuation date,
valuation date in the balance
reconciliation run stash table,
we have one valuation that yesterday we
had a discussion around this column,
right?
So I told,
I informed the team that it is not
earlier I mapped it with Sysdate,
but after so discussion with,
I updated this, OK.
And after that as per the discussion with,
we are checking whether the latest one,
if it is OK, it is related to, right?
OK, leave it.
OK.
Can you send me this new subject?
Yeah, yeah, I, I, I'll, I'll forward it.
Otherwise I'll send you the even subject
also I'll discuss with.
OK, Yeah, yeah.
Forward.
Because is,
is there any latest mail where like I'll
be able to see the entire thing, right?
Yeah, Yeah,
you will be able to see because lately I
have updated that active indicator in the
last week.
Why cleaning up the target table and I'm
not updating the current active indicator
to?
Why I'm just updating the expiration
indicator expiration date time for update
request, right?
But now I have added that and I have
updated like I informed the team also
here.
OK,
this is related to batch prerequisite
only.
You can ignore it but you can go through
it once.
What is happening there?
How this batch prerequisite,
OK batch prerequisite and batch task flow
would be interrelated are otherwise
connected at the stone branch scheduling
2 levels not here, not in IDMC.
How they have interrelated or how What
are the properties that discussion was
happened?
If you want detailed details,
you you can reach out to them Deepankar
or Durkesh, OK?
And they ask OK, one more thing here,
This is related to Nina.
This is related to yeah, this is sorry.
This is related to IDMC.
This we have to enable in our batch level
task flows OK which for our for each and
for our batch prerequisite and batch task
flow we have to use this option for
concurrent task.
For execution we have to select disable
concurrent execution OK,
OK after that this is the latest one.
I updated this row add to indicator part
OK.
And then this mail chain is done.
What else?
Daily status tracker.
Give me two minutes, I'll go back.
Yeah, hi, I'm back.
Let me share my screen again.
OK.
We have one ABC tab dedicatedly for ABC
statuses in daily status tracker.
So here all the metadata entries related
things are done.
We send it this for review also.
And all the components build is done.
These I have kept it 80% because this
needs to be revisited as part of
increment first time incremental load.
And all these 95% are Utah completed.
But the preview is not completed from we
have we have given the walkthrough,
but I I don't know,
but that's why I'm more like the any lead
has reviewed it.
OK, so like how how does it happen?
Like to test it you I did the I did the
end this thing and I have given this to
like component level review is done
common component level,
but end to end review UT document I
shared with time.
I think she has reviewed it already,
but I don't know like after that we are
using on ABC match.
So we I have not updated it,
but let it be like she has.
I,
I asked her like I like I I know after
breaking from ABC in one call,
there was a discussion around this UT
document that needs to be shared to
Bogdan and all.
So then spy I'm told that she has gone
through my document.
It is very exhaustive like that She was
she told.
So my UT document is also reviewed,
I guess and here.
So like is the ABC client was signed off
by client or like how it's not signed off?
It's not signed off it it's not signed
off.
I don't know like this increment first
time incremental design is also pending
and we know, right.
So this these design discussions were
going on Posted.
I was pulled into CC1I.
I was just doing work in CCMO posted.
So from the client side who reviews this,
I don't know.
Yeah, I don't know.
Once you implement this first time
incremental,
maybe after that you can check with
Nabrika or Swyam like to get the review
from client and get the sign off on LLD,
ABC,
all these things because we know that
there is something pending in ABC.
So we didn't go with the sign off.
I guess that is the reason why our team
didn't initiate that.
OK,
so you just like created all the MVC
components,
but nothing was reached out to client,
is it?
We had a walkthrough,
technical walkthrough already to the
client.
They they are OK,
They provided some feedback.
We had this like like I thought to
walkthrough of each and every component,
everything we had a walkthrough already,
they provided some feedback.
I incorporated it.
So who are these like these are these are
who provided the feedback.
I don't remember Bogdan, Tina and Chris.
I don't remember like out of these three
people who provided that like they were
people like Chris and team were there.
I don't know whether Bogdan is present or
not.
It was a in person collocation for U.S.
team.
So we had a like we had like we were we
joined online and they were in person
from onshore.
Oh client and our team.
You presented it that way?
Yeah, I presented it directly.
Yeah.
Oh, OK.
After that whatever the cheques feedbacks
they have given now I added this as part
and also the pending items.
So first time incremental is pending
still now till now it is pending.
I just want to know that execution time
type can be zoned to first time
incremental and batch return indicator
can be I these two are the details that I
got.
So you can use these two details while
you are designing and views.
I have updated the views as per the as
per the June 1 teams that is already done
whatever LO are done already,
there's the automation of D2 cheques in
the main mapping.
So we are doing it in the ETL logic right
in the in the source to stage mapping.
So they ask her like whether it can be
automated but told to park it aside.
And I raised at this point multiple times
they told me to mark it aside only.
So I parked it aside,
but it is already present here.
OK.
And then parameter file location and all
these things I have parameterized,
OK and all these things are done.
You,
you can ignore history catch upload is
not completed.
Lucid flow, it is done.
LED is done.
I can mark these two hours, OK,
based upon your inputs like I'll just
keep them invite only because after
development,
if you see that anything's needs to be
changed in the LLD or Lucid,
you can update it.
UT document is done folder structure
there is I don't know whether this has to
be followed,
followed up as part of ABC because
history load components would be specific
to specific domain, right?
So I don't know and this one question.
So is your thing making any changes in
any ABC component,
then we'll be doing it in the DIL common,
right?
And then again,
everything else needs to be refreshed or
pop it.
Yeah.
Again,
this is the main chain where we have to
inform team to refresh their mappings or
components in their APC folder.
Then again,
they have to like move it to the move
page.
They they have to just,
they have to just copy the component.
And if there is any snowflake connection,
they have to update it to their snowflake
connection to the domain specific
snowflake connection.
That's it.
There won't be much changes.
Yeah,
this is the requirement requirement from
the client.
They want ABC under each and every domain
folder.
This is their requirement.
OK,
these three are I think this is related
to Stone branch who can ignore like
whatever the one this one like new order
database setup.
OK, I told you right.
One team has not informed us OK and ABC
data.
Is there any any POC for that?
What do we need that POC Vidya and
Vaishnavi, OK, you can check with them.
OK, Vidya there.
OK.
And then last one is AABC data model
update.
We have created two more tables.
I have added them.
So whatever in white, right,
Those are not it.
Mostly you have to concentrate on first
time incremental load and this history
load.
Once these two are done,
just check with VAM or Needhika about the
automation of this and also new database.
All these things whatever kept blank
right, Just check with them, OK,
and last thing is prerequisites.
I told you right OK,
let me open the teams now here in the
snowflake.
I showed you already these videos,
but I'm just explaining you again.
So here we have entries for build and
this is for framework architecture,
whatever the framework at that time I
gave the KT to some testing team.
I guess this is the KT related to ABC
framework.
This,
these two are related to metadata entries.
How to make metadata entries?
And these this these three are related to
IDMC build and task flows OK.
And this this one OK,
this one is related to ABC integration
and this is related to ABC task flow
implement is the CCO are related to CCO
build OK.
And in this here IDMC build ABC
integration is there right?
This recording is the latest one which is
where I have showed how to integrate ABC
at the task floor level.
Like I told you to copy the component,
changing the parameter name and changing
the component's input fields,
all these things right?
I have done each and everything for
claims table and I recorded this session.
This is the prerequisite that I recorded
that session and you can use this the
first step and you can check first
framework and then this is the second
step.
And then we'll have to make entries into
the IDMC after that.
How to do the build these these two are
related to build and ABC integration.
Are these videos mentioned in the same
model that you are saying?
So yeah, here first one is there, right?
This is ABC integration.
This is a high level thing, OK.
And few and few recordings might have
same information because I have given it
CCO dedicatedly, right?
So that is there.
And these two are related to ABCABC meta
data entries, OK.
And then this is related to a CCO,
particularly CCO how to implement task
flow,
how to do metadata and this how to create
parameter with all these related to CCO.
And this is also related to CCO only
build, how to do the build OK,
these two are related to that we do only
Part 1, Part 2, OK.
And then ABC zone one ABC framework.
This is the Lucid level walkthrough which
I have given to testing team.
OK, that's it.
And all these records are available here.
And also you are also uploading all these
recordings into SharePoint, right?
Yeah.
If anybody want detailed walkthrough of
any components,
we can share all these things,
all these whatever we have discussed here,
we can share all this with them.
OK, I think I'm good.
Ria,
do you need anything else from my end?
I think today this already so sorry one
minute history.
I told you right history and catch up for
that we have a document now.
Let me give you the document watch.
Yeah, I'm just sharing.
We can be switching on It's already 2
hours.
So yeah, yeah.
And also but you,
you can you can go through it before we
the our KT code.
OK spy one minute.
I'm just checking the document.
Otherwise I miss it if I jump to CC one.
I shared the sheet name and document with
you can go through it.
You're asking something.
Yeah, today it is fine.
Let me go through this to like contact
team and tomorrow like what I was asking
today.
I think it's already 2 hours,
so like like keep it for tomorrow only.
So the tools and everything that you use,
whatever you know from your end,
just when you are asking, right,
IDMC or build overview,
how this project goes like that,
all this would be already covered in the
KT videos.
But tomorrow if you want,
I'll give you a high level thing that no
problem.
Yeah.
OK.
Yeah, then thank you.
Yeah, thank you, thank you.
Bye.